<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tracking the cargo on Fesco Help</title>
    <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tracking the cargo on Fesco Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is my container?</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/where_container/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/where_container/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. To find out where your container is:
— go to the tracking page;
   — вenter the container’s number or consignment note’s number in the search field (you can enter up to 4 numbers); — press “track the shipment”.

Step 2. To find out more information about the shipment, go to a detailed page in your account.
In “container’s voyage” block you can see all the information regarding the shipment’s activities and location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/customs_events/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/customs_events/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of the request in “Customs procedures” block you can find the information on the following customs procedures:
 inspection; measuring weight; x-ray inspection system.   Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     Смотрите также
 Where is my container?   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Invoices, certificates and B/Ls    Railway B/Ls    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customs declaration </title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/custom_declaration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/custom_declaration/</guid>
      <description>When the customs declaration is generated, it will appear on the detailed pade of the request in your account.  To access, download and copy the information in the declaration, press “Open”.
   Then press “download PDF”.
 Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     Смотрите также</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invoices, certificates and B/Ls</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/invoices-and-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/invoices-and-acts/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of the request in “invoices/certificates on the request” and “related documents” blocks you can find and download invoices, certificates and B/Ls on your request.
 Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     Смотрите также
 Where is my container?   Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Railway B/Ls    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Railway B/Ls</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/railway_bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/railway_bills/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of your request you can download the consignment notes in “Railway BLs” menu/block.
 Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     Смотрите также
 Where is my container?   Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Invoices, certificates and B/Ls     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>