<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Метод on Fesco Help</title>
    <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tags/%D0%BC%D0%B5%D1%82%D0%BE%D0%B4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Метод on Fesco Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://my.fesco.com/en/tags/%D0%BC%D0%B5%D1%82%D0%BE%D0%B4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RUB invoice – RUB payment</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/rouble-rouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/rouble-rouble/</guid>
      <description>Instructions on closing ruble invoices with ruble payments If the issued invoice is in rubles and the payment was made in rubles:
 In the left part of the window unbound payments are displayed. Choose one of the payments and tick the box next to it.  Currency must be ruble (RUR).    
 payment number – number of the payment order contract reference number – number used for payments payment date – date of carrying out banking operation payment amount – total amount of the payment unbound balance – amount to be paid payment currency – currency used to make the payment     In the bottom of the window you can see the details of the payment you selected:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request reconciliation reports</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/act_requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/act_requests/</guid>
      <description>а) **Go to ** “reconciliation report request”  and press “new request” or orange plus sign.
  б) Fill in the form in “information” block. 
 Enter your name (INN – identification tax number – and the name of the company – FIT LLC – will be entered automatically; Tick the numbers of contracts of which you need the reconciliation reports ; Indicate the period of reconciliation report; Add a comment (optional).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New request form</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/from_new_order/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/from_new_order/</guid>
      <description>а) Go to “my requests” page and press the orange button “new request”;  б) Choose the type of the request – New request;
  
в) Select the initial entries:
 Planned date of shipment, Route, Container type, Container’s owner;    
г) Choose the Rate, for selecting the rate press “select price”; you can filter the price rates by the Destination, Customs clearance location or Currency; then press “select the rate”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online request</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/</guid>
      <description>To make a request:   Through
“new request” form    From the
Calculator menu    From a previous
request (copy)    From template   
  Online application/request doesn’t need to be copied in written form. Online request is an official request for transportation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/</guid>
      <description>How to register an account
FAQ</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafts and templates</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/templates_and_drafts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/templates_and_drafts/</guid>
      <description>What is a draft?  Draft is a saved but not submitted request.  To save your draft press “save” instead of “submit the request” on new request page.
 What is a template?  Template is a request market with “template” tag. You can create a new request using a template.  Templates are connected to companies, not to users, therefore, one company’s users see the same templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uploading and submitting the documents</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/customs_documents/download_and_send/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/customs_documents/download_and_send/</guid>
      <description>How to upload and send the documents: а) go to ”Customs Declaration”;  б) find the container (in the filter on the left you can type the container’ number or B/L) and press “search”; 
    в) tap on your ID to go to your request page;  г) press “upload the documents” and select one of the uploading types:  — submit the documents in one package (in archive by one file)  — submit the document separately (separately send each document)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is my container?</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/where_container/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/where_container/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. To find out where your container is:
— go to the tracking page;
   — вenter the container’s number or consignment note’s number in the search field (you can enter up to 4 numbers); — press “track the shipment”.

Step 2. To find out more information about the shipment, go to a detailed page in your account.
In “container’s voyage” block you can see all the information regarding the shipment’s activities and location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Request</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/request/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/request/</guid>
      <description>On My access you can file a request for access to different sections/menus in your account and monitor the process of getting the access.  Completing access request form: а) Fill in the form: 
— Find the form using the sections menu, select the legal entity from the list.
  — Fill in the form with your details (the form may be partly filled in automatically):
 “Legal entity” field  - select the legal entity from the list; “Company of FESCO Group” field  - select one of the companies of FESCO Group; “Name of the signatory” field  - enter the signatory’s full name ; “Acting upon” field  - indicate the grounds; “Name of the party authorized by the Client to work with documents”  – enter the full name of the authorized party; “E-mail address of the party authorized by the Client to work with documents”  – enter an e-mail address of the authorized party; “Mobile phone of the party authorized by the Client to work with documents”  – enter a mobile phone of the authorized party  — Tick the box “I agree to the processing of my personal data”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules for payment binding</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/rules_of_binding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/rules_of_binding/</guid>
      <description>Automatic posting Invoices are processed and closed automatically based on the information indicated by the client in details of payment such as: contract, account number (indicating amount is optional). ). If the amount isn’t indicated, the invoice will be fully covered.   Examples of the information for indication in the details of payment for automatic processing are given below:   Example 1 (several invoices)::  Payment for logistics service, contract reference number № OME-15 /171 dated 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USD invoice - RUB payment</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/usd-rouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/usd-rouble/</guid>
      <description>Instruction for closing foreign currency invoices with payments in rubles If the invoice was issued in foreign currency, and you made payments in rubles:
 Unbound invoices are displayed in the left part of the window. Select one of the invoices and tick the box next to it.  The currency must be rubles (RUB)    
 payment number – number of the payment order contract reference number – number used for payments payment date – date of carrying out banking operation payment amount – total amount of the payment unbound balance – amount to be paid payment currency – currency used to make the payment     In the bottom of the window you can see the details of the payment you selected:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/customs_events/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/customs_events/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of the request in “Customs procedures” block you can find the information on the following customs procedures:
 inspection; measuring weight; x-ray inspection system.   Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     Смотрите также
 Where is my container?   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Invoices, certificates and B/Ls    Railway B/Ls    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using tags</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/tagging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/tagging/</guid>
      <description>Tags allow you to find a requst among other requests.  To tag or to create a new tag:  Go to “My requests”  Change a layout to Table Press “add” in the “tags” field Enter a new tag name and press Enter, or choose a tag from the list.      Tag is set!  
To find a request by the tag:  Go to “My requests”  Select tag’s name in the list Press “Search”      The requests were filtered by the tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request copies of documents </title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/duplicated_documents_requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/duplicated_documents_requests/</guid>
      <description>а) **Go to ** Requests for duplicate documents  and press “new request” or an orange plus sign.
  б) Fill in the form in “information” block: 
 Type in denomination (INN – identification tax number – and the name of the company FIT LLC will be entered automatically_) Press “select”, tick the documents that you need copies of (use search or filter); Leave a comment (optional).    в) Enter your contact information::</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request from the Calculator menu</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/from_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/from_calculator/</guid>
      <description>а) Go to “Calculator”;  б) Select initial entries:
 planned date of shipment, route, container type, container’s owner,  and press “calculate the price”;
  
в) select the rate and press “submit the request”    You can filter the rates by Destination, Customs clearance place and Currency 
  г) fill in the fields; fields marked with * are mandatory; and press “submit the request”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Как заполнять поля заявки</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/fields/</guid>
      <description>“ownership of the container” Field   Select “COC” if the container belongs to FESCO Select “SOC” if the container belongs to your or other entity.     “Legal entity” Field   Select one of the agreements to make a shipment request for it.    “Cargo name on B/L” Field   Enter actual name of the cargo For example, “Construction materials” or “Metal furniture”.    ETCNG - GNG Codes   Harmonized nomenclature of cargoes (GNG) CODE– usually corresponds to the first 8 numbers of Goods Nomenclature for Foreign Economic Activities (GNFEA) CODE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Additional documents uploading</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/customs_documents/reloading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/customs_documents/reloading/</guid>
      <description>To additionally upload and submit documents а) Go to ”Customs Declaration” and find your request;  б) Press “Additional documents upload”  The documents will be dismissed. After that you will be able to upload and submit the documents again.
   Additional uploading isn’t available for the documents in the following statuses:.  — container sent  — transit procedure finished  — documents were submitted to the Federal Customs Service of Russia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules for payment binding</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking the cargo</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/</guid>
      <description>To get the information on the shipment please go to your requests list and press open the request you need where you need to track the cargo:
   Information you will find on the detailed page of the request:
 Container’s location and performed operations (for example, receiving TLX-RELEASE from the shipper); Information on performed inspections, weight measuring and x-ray inspection; Customs documents and declaration; Invoices, certificates and B/Ls ; Railway B/Ls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New request from template</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/templates/</guid>
      <description>Use this feature for your repeating requests with the same details.  Шаг 1. To make an old request as a template:
 go to “list ot requests” change to Tablet layout press “add” make a tag “template” and press Enter or select the tag from the list.    
Шаг 2. To create a request based on a template:
 press “new request” button and select “from the template” find the request and press “submit again” fill in the fields, fields marked with * are mandatory; and press “submit the request”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All about requests</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/</guid>
      <description>####Что такое черновик? Черновик — это сохраненная, но не отправленная заявка.
Чтобы сохранить черновик, нажмите в новой заявке &amp;ldquo;Сохранить&amp;rdquo; вместо &amp;ldquo;Отправить заявку&amp;rdquo;.
####Что такое шаблон? Шаблон это заявка, которая отмечена тегом “шаблон”. Из шаблона можно создать новую заявку.
Как создавать заявку из шаблона
! Шаблоны привязываются к компаниям, а не пользователям. Т.е. все пользователи, привязанные к одной компании, увидят одни и те же шаблоны.
После попытки отправить заявку из шаблона или черновика, произойдёт проверка ставки и доступности выбранного рейса (для морской заявки).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customs documents</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/customs_documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/customs_documents/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of your request in “customs declaring procedure” block you can upload customs documents.
 Обязательные документы: 
 Invoice (proforma invoice); Packing list; Bill of lading; Forwarding contract – a contract for international shipment (freight forwarding), including the documents confirming agreement on the shipment (request for the shipmnet), and expenses connected to the shipment (shipment price, forwarder’s comission, additional expenses, customs duties and fees, and other expenses starting from the moment of the signing the contract and up to the delivery).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request from the Calculator menu</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/copy/</guid>
      <description>Use this feature if you want to make a new request using the previously entered info.  а) Go to “List of requests”;  б) Find a previous request and press “repeat”;
  
в) Fill in the fields; fields marked with * are mandatory; and press “submit the request”.
After sending the request you will get a notification with all the request details on your email.  You can continue the correspondence by sending a REPLY to the message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Examples of letters</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/sample_letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/sample_letter/</guid>
      <description>Example of a letter for closing
Example of a letter for clarification of the payment for a payment order
Example of a letter for partially closing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USD invoice - USD payment</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/usd-usd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/usd-usd/</guid>
      <description>Instructions for paying off foreign currency invoices with foreign currency payments. If the invoice was issued in foreign currency (not RUB), and the payment was made in the same foreign currency:
 Unbound invoices are displayed in the left part of the window. Select one of the invoices and tick the box next to it.  Currency of the payment must be not RUB (USD, EUR, CNY, KZT or other).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add new legal entity</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/new_client/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/new_client/</guid>
      <description>— Go to “Add new legal entity” subsection;  
— Enter INN of the legal entity;  
— Press “Find”. If there are a few companies with the same INN in the system, you will get a service notification. After this enter registration reason code (KPP) and press “find”.
 After completing the form successfully, the company will be added to your list as temporary, and you will be able to send an access request for any on the companies of FESCO Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request errors</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/errors/</guid>
      <description>In your account you can see several types of errors:    Your request validity has expired. 
Error cause: the quote has expired. What to do: set a new date for “planned shipment date”, after that select new quote by pressing “select price”. 
  No contract made for this type of shipment:
Error cause: probably you don’t have an additional agreement for working with electronic requests in your account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customs declaration </title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/custom_declaration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/custom_declaration/</guid>
      <description>When the customs declaration is generated, it will appear on the detailed pade of the request in your account.  To access, download and copy the information in the declaration, press “Open”.
   Then press “download PDF”.
 Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     Смотрите также</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/popular_questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/popular_questions/</guid>
      <description>How to restore a cancelled request?  Find the request, press “submit again”, then the request will be open for editing.
  When is the request moved to the archive? 
The request is moved to the archive in two cases:
 shipment completion, deleting the request in the account.  After the shipment completion the request is moved to the archive not immediately but when the closing documents are generated on this shipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statuses of the document</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/customs_documents/statuses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/customs_documents/statuses/</guid>
      <description>Statuses of the customs clearance documents can be the following: 
 Collecting the documents — the request is ready for collecting the documents;  Sent to the broker  — the documents were sent to the broker; Received by broker  — the documents were received by the broker; Checked by broker  — the documents were checked by the broker; Dismissed for editing  — the documents were dismissed by the clients for editing; Submitted to the Federal Customs Service of Russia /b&amp;gt; — пthe documents were submitted to the Federal Customs Service of Russia; Clearance procedure for transit is performed  — the transit was performed; the documents were assigned a transit declaration number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uploading documents</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/customs_documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/customs_documents/</guid>
      <description>Customs declaration menu allows to upload and send the documents for preliminary customs declaring procedure and control the terms of issuing documents.  
List of required documents for Clearance procedure for transit:  Invoice (proforma invoice) Packing list B/L Forwarding contract – a contract for international shipment (freight forwarding), including the documents confirming agreement son the shipment (request for the shipmnet), and expenses connected to the shipment (shipment price, forwarder’s comission, additional expenses, customs duties and fees, and other expenses starting from the moment of the signing the contract and up to the delivery).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View the RECEIPTS</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/closed_payment_orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/closed_payment_orders/</guid>
      <description>View what invoices were used to cover the receipt.  In “unbound payments” block (on the left) select the payment for detalization:  
 Go to “bound payments” (on the right):
    
Then you will see a table with all the information on the right:
 Date, amount, invoice number ;  Date, amount, payment number;  Contract number   Use horizontal scroll to view the information in the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invoices, certificates and B/Ls</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/invoices-and-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/invoices-and-acts/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of the request in “invoices/certificates on the request” and “related documents” blocks you can find and download invoices, certificates and B/Ls on your request.
 Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     Смотрите также
 Where is my container?   Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Railway B/Ls    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Railway B/Ls</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/railway_bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/railway_bills/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of your request you can download the consignment notes in “Railway BLs” menu/block.
 Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     Смотрите также
 Where is my container?   Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Invoices, certificates and B/Ls     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electronic archive</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/</guid>
      <description>In this menu you can find all the closing documents of your shipments, download them in archive, and send requests for reconciliation reports and copies of the documents.  Documents list: To see the closing documents on your shipments, go to Electronic archive .
To download a single document, press the icon in column “Document (1)”.  To download all the documents on your shipment, press the icon “download documents’ package” (2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment binding</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/schedule/</guid>
      <description>To see the timetable:
 Go to “schedule of the services” ; Enter necessary information; Press “find a schedule”.   Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы? Отправить запрос     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to register an account</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/instruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/instruction/</guid>
      <description>• Access and complete the registration form;  • Wait for the confirmation code in SMS from FESCO to your mobile number;  • Enter the confirmation code in the registration form;  • Log-in password will be sent to your e-mail and phone number. 
INN (taxpayer identification number) number and e-mail entered during the registration will be used for accessing the system and sending notifications from your account for making requests and for other operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download the documents in archive file</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/archive_zip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/archive_zip/</guid>
      <description>To download the documents in archive file:
а) Go to the documents list in Electronic archive menu;  б) ВTick the documents needed;  в) Press “download archive”; 
  г) Wait until the download status changes from “processing” to “finished” and press “open”;  д) Press “Download”; 
  The archive file will be downloaded to your computer.
Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/questions/</guid>
      <description>If you didn&amp;#39;t receive a password on your e-mail   Check spam and low-priority folders. Message us in the chat on our web-site.   What is a full and limited access to the account?  After registration you will get a limited access to your account.  You can use the following functions:    Public access Limited access Full access     The calculator of shipment price         Filing requests for quotations         Filing requests for transportations         Saving drafts order         Copy orders         Container tracking and shipment status         Downloading and checking status of the customs documents         Entering the data on VGM         Contacts and bills         Chat with a manager</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/questions/</guid>
      <description>How to add one more cargo to the request?  In GNG CODE field enter the code for collected cargoes: 99020000 In “additional requirements” field indicate detailed information for the cargoes.    Where is the information about door delivery? 
In “additional requirements” field.    Who can I indicate as a consignee at the destination station? 
In case of FESCO removal, &amp;ldquo;FIT agent&amp;rdquo; is indicated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>