<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Electronic archive on Fesco Help</title>
    <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Electronic archive on Fesco Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Request reconciliation reports</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/act_requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/act_requests/</guid>
      <description>а) **Go to ** “reconciliation report request”  and press “new request” or orange plus sign.
  б) Fill in the form in “information” block. 
 Enter your name (INN – identification tax number – and the name of the company – FIT LLC – will be entered automatically; Tick the numbers of contracts of which you need the reconciliation reports ; Indicate the period of reconciliation report; Add a comment (optional).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request copies of documents </title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/duplicated_documents_requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/duplicated_documents_requests/</guid>
      <description>а) **Go to ** Requests for duplicate documents  and press “new request” or an orange plus sign.
  б) Fill in the form in “information” block: 
 Type in denomination (INN – identification tax number – and the name of the company FIT LLC will be entered automatically_) Press “select”, tick the documents that you need copies of (use search or filter); Leave a comment (optional).    в) Enter your contact information::</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download the documents in archive file</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/archive_zip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/archive_zip/</guid>
      <description>To download the documents in archive file:
а) Go to the documents list in Electronic archive menu;  б) ВTick the documents needed;  в) Press “download archive”; 
  г) Wait until the download status changes from “processing” to “finished” and press “open”;  д) Press “Download”; 
  The archive file will be downloaded to your computer.
Были ли эта статья полезной? Да  Нет    Пользователи, считающие этот материал полезным  из  Еще есть вопросы?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>