<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fesco Help</title>
    <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fesco Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://my.fesco.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RUB invoice – RUB payment</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/rouble-rouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/rouble-rouble/</guid>
      <description>Instructions on closing ruble invoices with ruble payments If the issued invoice is in rubles and the payment was made in rubles:
1) In the left part of the window unbound payments are displayed. Choose one of the payments and tick the box next to it.  Currency must be ruble (RUR).
  
 payment number – number of the payment order agreement number – number used for payments date of payment – date of carrying out banking operation payment amount – total amount of the payment unbound balance – amount to be paid payment currency – currency used to make the payment    2) In the bottom of the window you can see the details of the payment you selected:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request reconciliation reports</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/act_requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/act_requests/</guid>
      <description>a) Go to “Reconciliation report request”  and press “New pachage of documents” or orange plus sign.
  b) Fill in the form in “information” block. 
 Enter your name (INN – identification tax number – and the name of the company – FIT LLC – will be entered automatically; Tick the numbers of contracts of which you need the reconciliation reports ; Indicate the period of reconciliation report; Add a comment (optional).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New request form</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/from_new_order/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/from_new_order/</guid>
      <description>a) Go to “My Orders page” and press the orange button “New order”;  b) Choose the type of the request – New order;
  
c) Select the initial entries:
 Data of dispatch, Route, Container type, Container ownership;    
d) Choose the Rate, for selecting the rate press “Select offer”; you can filter the price rates by the Destination, Customs clearance location or Currency; then press “Select offer”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafts and templates</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/templates_and_drafts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/templates_and_drafts/</guid>
      <description>What is a draft?  Draft is a saved but not submitted request.  To save your draft press “Save” instead of “Create” on new request page.
 What is a template?  Template is a request market with “template” tag. You can create a new request using a template.  Templates are connected to companies, not to users, therefore, one company’s users see the same templates.
After submitting a request using the template or draft, rate and availability of selected voyage (for maritime shipment) will be checked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is my container?</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/where_container/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/where_container/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. To find out where your container is:
— go to the tracking page;
   — enter the container’s number or consignment note’s number in the search field (you can enter up to 4 numbers); — press “Search”.
 Step 2. To find out more information about the shipment, go to a detailed page in your account.
In “Vehicles” block you can see all the information regarding the shipment’s activities and location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Request</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/request/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/request/</guid>
      <description>On My access you can file a request for access to different sections/menus in your account and monitor the process of getting the access.  Completing access request form: а) Fill in the form: 
— Find the form using the sections menu, select the legal entity from the list.
  — Fill in the form with your details (the form may be partly filled in automatically):
 “Your legal entity” field  - select the legal entity from the list; “FESCO GC Group” field  - select one of the companies of FESCO Group; “Name of signer of SA” field  - enter the signatory’s full name ; “Valid Based” field  - indicate the grounds; “Name of the person authorized by the Client to perform actions with documents”  – enter the full name of the authorized party; “E-mail Adress the mail of the person authorized by the Client to perform actions with documents”  – enter an e-mail address of the authorized party; “Mobile phone of the person authorized by the Client to perform actions with documents”  – enter a mobile phone of the authorized party  — Tick the box “I agree to processing of personal data”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USD invoice - RUB payment</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/usd-rouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/usd-rouble/</guid>
      <description>Instruction for closing foreign currency invoices with payments in rubles If the invoice was issued in foreign currency, and you made payments in rubles:
1) Unbound invoices are displayed in the left part of the window. Select one of the invoices and tick the box next to it.  The currency must be rubles (RUB)
  
 payment number – number of the payment order agreement number – number used for payments date of payment – date of carrying out banking operation payment amount – total amount of the payment unbound balance – amount to be paid payment currency – currency used to make the payment    2) In the bottom of the window you can see the details of the payment you selected:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/customs_events/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/customs_events/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of the request in “Customs events” block you can find the information on the following customs procedures:
 inspection; measuring weight; x-ray inspection system.   Was this article helpful? Yes  No    Users that counts this article helpful  of  Is there any questions? Send a request     See also
 Where is my container?   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Invoices, certificates and B/Ls    Railway B/Ls    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using tags</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/tagging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/tagging/</guid>
      <description>Tags allow you to find a requst among other requests.  To tag or to create a new tag:  Go to “My orders”  Change a layout to Table Press “Add” in the “Tags” field Enter a new tag name and press Enter, or choose a tag from the list.      Tag is set!  
To find a request by the tag:  Go to “My orders”  Select tag’s name in the list Press “Search”      The requests were filtered by the tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request copies of documents </title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/duplicated_documents_requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/duplicated_documents_requests/</guid>
      <description>a) Go to Requests for duplicate documents  and press “new request” or an orange plus sign.
  b) Fill in the form in “information” block: 
 Type in denomination (INN – identification tax number – and the name of the company FIT LLC will be entered automatically_) Press “select”, tick the documents that you need copies of (use search or filter); Leave a comment (optional).    c) Enter your contact information::</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to fill in the fields in the request</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/fields/</guid>
      <description>“Container ownership” field   Select “COC” if the container belongs to FESCO Select “SOC” if the container belongs to your or other entity.     “Legal entity” field   Select one of the agreements to make a shipment request for it.    “Cargo name on B/L” field   Enter actual name of the cargo For example, “Construction materials” or “Metal furniture”.    ETCNG - GNG Codes   Harmonized nomenclature of cargoes (GNG) CODE– usually corresponds to the first 8 numbers of Goods Nomenclature for Foreign Economic Activities (GNFEA) CODE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request from the Calculator menu</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/from_calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/from_calculator/</guid>
      <description>a) Go to “Calculator”;  b) Select initial entries:
 date of dispatch, route, container type, container owner,  and press “Get rate”;
  
c) select the rate and press “Make order”    You can filter the rates by Point of Destination, Place of customs clearance place and Offers currency 
  d) fill in the fields; fields marked with * are mandatory; and press “Create”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New request from template</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/templates/</guid>
      <description>Use this feature for your repeating requests with the same details.  Step 1. To make an old request as a template:
 go to “My orders” change to Tablet layout press “Add” make a tag “template” and press Enter or select the tag from the list.    
Step 2. To create a request based on a template:
 press “New order” button and select “From template” find the request and press “Repeat” fill in the fields, fields marked with * are mandatory; and press “Create”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copy from the previous request</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/new_order/online_order/copy/</guid>
      <description>Use this feature if you want to make a new request using the previously entered info.  а) Go to “My orders”;  б) Find a previous request and press “Repeat”;
  
в) Fill in the fields; fields marked with * are mandatory; and press “Create”.
After sending the request you will get a notification with all the request details on your email.  You can continue the correspondence by sending a REPLY to the message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USD invoice - USD payment</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/usd-usd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/instruction_of_binding/usd-usd/</guid>
      <description>Instructions for paying off foreign currency invoices with foreign currency payments. If the invoice was issued in foreign currency (not RUB), and the payment was made in the same foreign currency:
1) Unbound invoices are displayed in the left part of the window. Select one of the invoices and tick the box next to it.  Currency of the payment must be not RUB (USD, EUR, CNY, KZT or other).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add new legal entity</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/new_client/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/new_client/</guid>
      <description>— Go to “Add new legal entity” subsection;  
— Enter INN of the legal entity;  
— Press “Find”. If there are a few companies with the same INN in the system, you will get a service notification. After this enter registration reason code (KPP) and press “find”.
 After completing the form successfully, the company will be added to your list as temporary, and you will be able to send an access request for any on the companies of FESCO Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request errors</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/errors/</guid>
      <description>In your account you can see several types of errors:    Your request validity has expired. 
Error cause: the quote has expired. What to do: set a new date for “planned shipment date”, after that select new quote by pressing “select price”. 
  No contract made for this type of shipment.
Error cause: probably you don’t have an additional agreement for working with electronic requests in your account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customs declaration </title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/custom_declaration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/custom_declaration/</guid>
      <description>When the customs declaration is generated, it will appear on the detailed pade of the request in your account.  To access, download and copy the information in the declaration, press “Open”.
   Then press “Create PDF download”.
 Was this article helpful? Yes  No    Users that counts this article helpful  of  Is there any questions? Send a request     See also</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View the RECEIPTS</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/closed_payment_orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/payments_and_invoices/closed_payment_orders/</guid>
      <description>View what invoices were used to cover the receipt.  In “unbound payments” block (on the left) select the payment for detalization:  
 Go to “Tied payments” (on the right):
    
Then you will see a table with all the information on the right:
 Date, amount, invoice number ;  Date, amount, payment number;  Contract number   Use horizontal scroll to view the information in the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invoices, certificates and B/Ls</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/invoices-and-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/invoices-and-acts/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of the request in “Invoices/acts on request” and “Railway bills” blocks you can find and download invoices, certificates and B/Ls on your request.
 Was this article helpful? Yes  No    Users that counts this article helpful  of  Is there any questions? Send a request     See also
 Where is my container?   Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Railway B/Ls    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Railway Bills</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/railway_bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/tracking/railway_bills/</guid>
      <description>On the detailed page of your request you can download the consignment notes in “Railway Bills” menu/block.
 Was this article helpful? Yes  No    Users that counts this article helpful  of  Is there any questions? Send a request     See also
 Where is my container?   Inspection, weight measuring and x-ray inspection   Customs documents   Customs declaration   Invoices, certificates and B/Ls     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to register an account</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/instruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/instruction/</guid>
      <description>• Access and complete the registration form;  • Wait for the confirmation code in SMS from FESCO to your mobile number;  • Enter the confirmation code in the registration form;  • Log-in password will be sent to your e-mail and phone number. 
INN (taxpayer identification number) number and e-mail entered during the registration will be used for accessing the system and sending notifications from your account for making requests and for other operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download the documents in archive file</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/archive_zip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/elar/archive_zip/</guid>
      <description>To download the documents in archive file:
a) Go to the documents list in Electronic archive menu;  b) Tick the documents needed;  c) Press “Download archive”; 
  d) Wait until the download status changes from “In process” to “Done” and press “Open”;    e) Press “Download”; 
  The archive file will be downloaded to your computer.
Was this article helpful? Yes  No    Users that counts this article helpful  of  Is there any questions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/registration/questions/</guid>
      <description>If you didn&amp;#39;t receive a password on your e-mail   Check spam and low-priority folders. Message us in the chat on our web-site.   What is a full and limited access to the account?  After registration you will get a limited access to your account.  You can use the following functions:    Public access Limited access Full access     The calculator of shipment price         Filing requests for quotations         Filing requests for transportations         Saving drafts order         Copy orders         Container tracking and shipment status         Downloading and checking status of the customs documents         Entering the data on VGM         Contacts and bills         Chat with a manager</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>