<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All about requests on Fesco Help</title>
    <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/</link>
    <description>Recent content in All about requests on Fesco Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drafts and templates</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/templates_and_drafts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/templates_and_drafts/</guid>
      <description>What is a draft?  Draft is a saved but not submitted request.  To save your draft press “save” instead of “submit the request” on new request page.
 What is a template?  Template is a request market with “template” tag. You can create a new request using a template.  Templates are connected to companies, not to users, therefore, one company’s users see the same templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using tags</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/tagging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/tagging/</guid>
      <description>Tags allow you to find a requst among other requests.  To tag or to create a new tag:  Go to “My requests”  Change a layout to Table Press “add” in the “tags” field Enter a new tag name and press Enter, or choose a tag from the list.      Tag is set!  
To find a request by the tag:  Go to “My requests”  Select tag’s name in the list Press “Search”      The requests were filtered by the tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request errors</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/all_orders/errors/</guid>
      <description>In your account you can see several types of errors:    Your request validity has expired. 
Error cause: the quote has expired. What to do: set a new date for “planned shipment date”, after that select new quote by pressing “select price”. 
  No contract made for this type of shipment:
Error cause: probably you don’t have an additional agreement for working with electronic requests in your account.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>