<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My accesses on Fesco Help</title>
    <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My accesses on Fesco Help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://my.fesco.com/en/access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Request</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/request/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/request/</guid>
      <description>On My access you can file a request for access to different sections/menus in your account and monitor the process of getting the access.  Completing access request form: а) Fill in the form: 
— Find the form using the sections menu, select the legal entity from the list.
  — Fill in the form with your details (the form may be partly filled in automatically):
 “Your legal entity” field  - select the legal entity from the list; “FESCO GC Group” field  - select one of the companies of FESCO Group; “Name of signer of SA” field  - enter the signatory’s full name ; “Valid Based” field  - indicate the grounds; “Name of the person authorized by the Client to perform actions with documents”  – enter the full name of the authorized party; “E-mail Adress the mail of the person authorized by the Client to perform actions with documents”  – enter an e-mail address of the authorized party; “Mobile phone of the person authorized by the Client to perform actions with documents”  – enter a mobile phone of the authorized party  — Tick the box “I agree to processing of personal data”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add new legal entity</title>
      <link>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/new_client/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://my.fesco.com/en/access/new_client/</guid>
      <description>— Go to “Add new legal entity” subsection;  
— Enter INN of the legal entity;  
— Press “Find”. If there are a few companies with the same INN in the system, you will get a service notification. After this enter registration reason code (KPP) and press “find”.
 After completing the form successfully, the company will be added to your list as temporary, and you will be able to send an access request for any on the companies of FESCO Group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>